Andrew Paolo Solbjor

- Stockton, California, United States. - (209)-641-6122 - s0lbjorandr3w@gmail.com - GitHub/Solbjor

Professional Objectives

I am interested in applying and improving my programming abilities to improve my skills in developing useful applications. I am also interested in furthering my knowledge and abilities via a position where I can expand my current experience and successfully apply my skills to manage and troubleshoot physical devices and inter-networking systems.

Education

- San Joaquin Delta College, Stockton, California, United States. (Transferred)
- Sacramento State University, Sacramento, California, United States. Bachelors in Science, Computer Science. (In Progress)

Skills

Microsoft Office, Python, C++, Java, Kotlin, AI, Flutter, project management skills, interpersonal communication skills, problem solving, troubleshooting.

Professional Experience

Teaching Assistant internship

05/17/2023 - 10/25/2023

SJDC Verizon Innovative Learning Summer Camp, Stockton, United States

- Taught Python programming to middle school students.
 - Promoted participation and encouragement in STEM among youth.

Support Services Internship

10/01/2019 - 12/01/2019

Align Technology, Costa Rica

• Data analysis and management.

Projects

Medipal Concluded

Medical information and patients tracking app designed for use in rural communities in developing countries. Skills Obtained:

- Flutter frontend/backend development.
- Team leadership and management.
- Firebase integration and usage.

Volunteer Experience Extracurricular

Verizon Innovative Learning Program:

03/2023 - 11/2023

- Volunteered 210 hours in the STEM enrichment program.
- Educated children in the basics of block coding.

Physics, Math, Computer Science Projects Club:

09/2022 - 12/2023

• Treasurer, managed club funds and organized events.

Languages

English - Written and spoken - Native speaker

Spanish - Written and spoken - Fluent